hundred years before a
Seven
nail was ever driven
Roman
wrist,
human
through a
wrote
Jerusalem
a prophet in
of a
death
down the
he had never met.
man
wounds,
He described the
silence,
the
grave
in
man
and the rich
death.
his
what
down
He even wrote
were for.
wounds
the
he asked the
then
And
over
hangs
question that still
page:
the
our report?
believed
"Who hath
is the
whom
and to
revealed?"
LORD
arm of the
fifty-three.
Isaiah
This is
it is the most
Either
of
all
astonishing accident in
literature
human
standing outside of
someone
or
us,
telling
time was
early,
centuries
would save
God
exactly how
world.
the
Himself
It opens with God
pointing.
"Behold,
prudently,
deal
my servant shall
and
exalted
he shall be
extolled,
high."
very
and be
yourself for a
brace
You
king.
conquering
the picture breaks.
then
And
visage was so marred
"…his
man,
any
more than
than
more
and his form
a
men…"
the sons of
past recognising.
beaten
face
nor
form
"…he hath no
comeliness;
we shall see
when
and
him,
that
beauty
there is no
him.
desire
we should
and rejected
despised
He is
men;
of
of sorrows,
man
a
with grief…"
acquainted
and
does not
Servant
God's chosen
in armour.
arrive
in agony.
arrives
He
looks at him
world
The
away.
and looks
one and the
exalted
The
one are the same
despised
man.
two together
those
Hold
is the whole
tension
that
in a single breath.
gospel
comes the centre of
Then
line
the chapter and every
transaction.
is a
our
borne
"Surely he hath
griefs,
our sorrows…" our
carried
and
griefs.
own.
Not his
for
wounded
"But he was
transgressions,
our
for our
bruised
he was
iniquities:
of our peace
chastisement
the
him;
upon
was
stripes we
his
and with
on the
Stay
are healed."
words.
small
transgressions.
Our
peace.
wounds.
His
good
This is not a
as a brave
dying
man
example.
substitution:
This is a
in the place
stands
one
and takes what
many
of
earned.
they had
think
And in case you
this from
watching
you are
distance,
a safe
reaches out and pulls
Isaiah
in:
you
we like sheep have
"All
astray;
gone
every one
turned
we have
way;
own
to his
hath laid
LORD
and the
of
iniquity
on him the
of us.
All
us all."
one.
Every
named
The straying is
the rescue:
then
and
on him.
laid
how he suffers.
watch
Then
oppressed,
"He was
afflicted,
and he was
not his
opened
yet he
mouth:
as a
brought
he is
slaughter,
lamb to the
before
and as a sheep
dumb,
her shearers is
not his
openeth
so he
defence.
mouth." No
on his accusers.
curse
No
Silent.
question.
honest
Now an
Jewish
For centuries many thoughtful
Servant
readers have understood this
man,
not as one
of
nation
but as the
itself
Israel
people,
suffering
a
among the nations.
despised
real
And they have a
them.
behind
text
in this same book,
Earlier
calls the nation by
God
title:
very
this
servant,
my
"…Thou art
Israel,
O
I will be
whom
in
chapter fifty-three
reading
glorified." So
is not a
Israel
as
dodge.
first
natural
It is the
guess.
answer,
serious
It deserves a
sneer.
not a
chapter
Here is what the
that no nation can
does
survive.
First,
is sinless:
sufferer
the
with
grave
"…he made his
wicked,
the
in
rich
and with the
death;
his
no
done
because he had
violence,
was any deceit in
neither
in
people
his mouth." No
nation,
history not a
faithful
not even its most
has ever been honestly
remnant
way.
described that
Second,
for the people:
dies
he
of my
transgression
"…for the
was he stricken." The
people
in their place
stands
Servant
simply be
cannot
so he
them.
grave.
single
A
tomb.
man's
A rich
life.
sinless
A
people.
This is not a
This
person.
is a
question
only
Which leaves the
matters.
that
Who
he?
is
Testament records the
New
The
someone asked it
moment
exact
loud.
out
a
Ethiopia
A man from
home
riding
court official is
chariot,
in his
this very chapter aloud:
reading
as a
led
"…He was
slaughter;
sheep to the
dumb
lamb
and like a
shearer,
before his
he not his
opened
so
Philip,
mouth…"
Spirit,
sent by the
the chariot.
alongside
comes
turns and
Ethiopian
And the
seems
Isaiah
asks the question
invite:
to
thee,
pray
"I
speaketh the prophet
whom
of
this?
himself,
of
man?"
other
or of some
gives the answer
Luke
And
line.
unforgettable
in one
opened his mouth,
Philip
"Then
at the same
began
and
scripture,
Jesus."
and preached unto him
not have to
did
He
the text into shape.
wrestle
fifty-three,
Isaiah
He started at
led straight
road
and the
Nazareth.
to Jesus of
wondered if
Isaiah
The report
would believe the New
anyone
answers:
Testament
man.
this is the
line
But there is one
than
heavier
in this chapter
wounds.
all the
LORD
"Yet it pleased the
him;
bruise
to
put him to
hath
he
Pleased.
grief…"
delights
Father
Not because the
pain
in
delights
but because He
would accomplish:
cross
what the
home.
a people brought
is no
Servant
And the
gears
victim caught in the
says he "poured out
Isaiah
unto death."
soul
his
it.
gave
He
Then,
quietly,
morning.
the chapter turns toward
see his seed,
shall
"…he
his days,
prolong
he shall
of the
pleasure
and the
shall prosper in his
LORD
hand.
of the
see
He shall
of his soul,
travail
A
satisfied…"
and shall be
bruised to death does
man
to see his
live
not
prolonged
days
is not the
death
unless
of him.
end
does not spell out
Isaiah
tomb
an empty
a shape
leaves
but he
resurrection fills,
only
that
Testament
a shadow the New
into full light.
bring
would
note
final
And the chapter's
is not
Servant
over the
word:
one
defeat but
satisfied.
was not wasted.
travail
The
enough.
It was
where
So come back to
began.
Isaiah
our report?
believed
"Who hath
is the
whom
and to
of the LORD revealed?"
arm
of the LORD
The
strength of God
saving
the
thing.
is not a
person.
It is a
face,
It has a
more than any man's.
marred
hands,
has
It
for transgressions that were
wounded
his own.
never
name
And it has your
six.
verse
in
it names "we
straying
The
every one to
turned
have
way"
own
his
yours,
is
mine.
and
where the sentence
read
But
ends:
hath laid on
LORD
"the
of us
iniquity
him the
all."
that
turned
Every way you
own
was your
on him.
laid
carried.
Already
taken away.
not have to
do
You
yourself up before you
clean
come.
point
That is the whole
fifty-three:
Isaiah
of
for your
wounded
he was
transgressions,
them in your
bore
and
place.
true.
The report is
LORD
The arm of the
name.
has a
name
His
Jesus.
is
the report?
believed
Have you