has an opinion about
Everyone
Jesus.
teacher,
A good
prophet,
a
example,
a moral
myth,
a
savior.
does not leave
Jesus
But
in the crowd.
question
the
16,
Matthew
In
what
disciples
he asked his
about him.
saying
people were
answers.
They gave the public
made it personal.
Jesus
Then
say
But who do you
am?
I
that
ends second -hand
question
That
faith.
answer,
family's
Not your
answer,
pastor's
not your
answer.
internet's
not the
Yours.
Jesus
Because you can admire
and still
distance
from a
Lord.
never confess Him as
answered,
Peter
Christ,
You are the
of the living
Son
the
God.
said this was
Jesus
And
blood.
not flesh and
from the
revelation
It was
Father.
see
truly
We do not
opens our
God
Jesus unless
eyes.
scroll,
So before you
honestly.
answer
Jesus
Who do you say
is?