Everyone
has an opinion about
Jesus.
A good
teacher,
a
prophet,
a moral
example,
a
myth,
savior.
But
Jesus
does not leave
the
question
in the crowd.
In
Matthew
16,
he asked his
disciples
what
people were
saying
about him.
They gave the public
answers.
Then
Jesus
made it personal.
But who do you
say
that
I
am?
That
question
ends second -hand
faith.
Not your
family's
answer,
not your
pastor's
answer,
not the
internet's
answer.
Yours.
Because you can admire
Jesus
from a
distance
and still
never confess Him as
Lord.
Peter
answered,
You are the
Christ,
the
Son
of the living
God.
And
Jesus
said this was
not flesh and
blood.
It was
revelation
from the
Father.
We do not
truly
see
Jesus unless
God
opens our
eyes.
So before you
scroll,
answer
honestly.
Who do you say
Jesus
is?