opens with one
twenty-two
Psalm
alone
dying
forsaken man
nation
every
and ends with
earth.
on
suffering,
After the
its arms
throws
the song
nation:
open to every
of the
ends
"All the
and turn
remember
world shall
the LORD:
unto
of
the kindreds
all
and
before
shall worship
nations
the
thee."
in one
dying
A man
Empire
Roman
corner of the
says the
song
and his
will
earth
ends of the
God.
turn to
impossible.
It sounded
cross,
But from that
tomb,
and the empty
went out and
gospel
the
nation
nation after
people in
LORD,
the
have turned to
died
who
the One
worshipping
rose.
and
of
reach
That is the
cross.
the
a local
never
It was
tragedy
nations,
it was for the
of the
the kindreds
all
earth.
of the
ends
And "the
you are,
wherever
includes
world"
now.
right
with
that began
song
The
alone has
dying
one man
earth;
whole
swept the
still
it promised
Lord
the
to
room for you
has
to Him.
turn