You can be
completely
full
and still feel
empty.
Fridge
docked,
day went
fine,
and
something
deeper than your
stomach
is still hungry.
That ache isn't a
flawed
affix,
it's a
signpost.
You were
built
to be
filled by
someone,
not
something.
Hear
him.
I am the
bread
of
life.
He that
cometh
to me
shall never
hunger,
and he that
believeth
on
me shall never
thirst.
Not less
hungry,
never.
So you keep
reaching
for
the next
thing,
plate,
the next
purchase,
person,
asking
created
things to do
what only
Christ
can do.
Stop
feeding
a soul hunger
with
things
that spoil.
Come to the
bread
of
life,
not a
snack
for the
moment,
but the life your
soul
was
made
for.