full
completely
You can be
empty.
and still feel
stocked,
Fridge
fine
day went
deeper than your
something
and
is still hungry.
stomach
a flaw
isn't
That ache
fix.
to
signpost.
It's a
to be
built
You were
Someone,
filled by
something.
not
Him:
Hear
of
bread
"I am the
life:
to me
cometh
he that
hunger;
shall never
on
believeth
and he that
Not
me shall never thirst."
hungry.
less
Never.
for
reaching
So you keep
thing
the next
plate,
purchase,
the next
person
things to do
created
asking
can do.
Christ
what only
with
soul-hunger
Stop feeding a
that spoil.
things
of
Bread
Come to the
life
for the
snack
not a
moment,
soul
but the life your
for.
made
was