they shook
cross
At the
the
and sneered
heads
their
had
psalm
very taunt a
before,
years
thousand
recorded a
22.
psalm
David,
and dying
mocked
describing a
man,
words.
tormentors
his
writes
even
head,
They shake the
saying,
Lord
the
he trusted on
deliver him,
would
that he
him.
deliver
let him
later,
years
A thousand
cross,
at the
records both.
Matthew
their
wagging
The passers -by
heads,
jeering.
leaders
religious
and the
God,
He trusted in
him now.
deliver
let him
gesture,
The same
taunt,
the same
people
by
flung at him
saw what they
never
who
echoing.
were
him,
deliver
Let him
sneered.
they
delivered,
wasn't
And he
lacked the
Jesus
not because
down,
power to come
every power.
had
he
staying was
because
He stayed
to deliver
way
the only
you.
him
pinned
weakness
They thought
cross.
to that
love.
It was
down
come
He could have
instant.
in an
with
stay
He chose to
view.
you in